Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files P-T, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files A
  - Subject Files
    - Scott, Mildred (Box A-107, Folder 253)
    - Scott, N.H. (Rev.) (Box A-107, Folder 254)
      Photographer if identified: Burr's Studio
    - Scott, Nancy (Box A-107, Folder 255)
    - Scott, Nathaniel (Box A-107, Folder 256)
    - Scott, Neil (Box A-107, Folder 257)
    - Scott, Noel H. (Rev.) (Box A-107, Folder 258)
    - Scott, Osborne E. (Box A-107, Folder 259)
    - Scott, Oz (Box A-107, Folder 260)
    - Scott, Patricia (Box A-107, Folder 261)
    - Scott, Pereta (Box A-107, Folder 262)
    - Scott, Perry (Box A-107, Folder 263)
    - Scott, Phyllis (Box A-107, Folder 264)
      Photographer if identified: Altman-Pach Studio
    - Scott, Q.D. (Box A-107, Folder 265)
    - Scott, Randolph (Box A-107, Folder 266)
    - Scott, Randy (Box A-107, Folder 267)
    - Scott, Ray (Box A-107, Folder 268)
    - Scott, Ray (Box A-107, Folder 269)
    - Scott, Raymond (Box A-107, Folder 270)
    - Scott, Robert, Jr. (Box A-107, Folder 271)
    - Scott, Roberta (Box A-107, Folder 272)
    - Scott, Roland B. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-107, Folder 273)
      Photographer if identified: Scurlock Studios
    - Scott, Ronald (Box A-107, Folder 274)
    - Scott, Seret (Box A-107, Folder 275)
    - Scott, Shirley (Box A-107, Folder 276)
    - Scott, Teen (Mrs.) (Box A-107, Folder 277)
    - Scott, Theodore & Agnes Scott (Box A-107, Folder 278)
    - Scott, Terry (Box A-107, Folder 279)
    - Scott, Theoper (Box A-107, Folder 280)
    - Scott, Thomas H. (Box A-107, Folder 281)
    - Scott, Tina (Box A-107, Folder 282)
    - Scott, Tom (Box A-107, Folder 283)
    - Scott, Tommy (Box A-107, Folder 284)
    - Scott, Tyrone (Box A-107, Folder 285)
    - Scott, Vivian (See Rev. Robert Bullock) (Box A-108, Folder 1)
    - Scott, W. A. (Box A-108, Folder 2)
    - Scott, Wendell (Box A-108, Folder 3)
    - Scott, Wendell (Box A-108, Folder 4)
    - Scott, William Mr & Mrs. (Box A-108, Folder 5)
    - Scott, William B. (Box A-108, Folder 6)
    - Scott, Wm. L. (Box A-108, Folder 7)
    - Scott, Willie (Box A-108, Folder 8)
    - Scott, Winona L. (Box A-108, Folder 9)
    - Scott, Yvonne (Box A-108, Folder 10)
    - Scott-Gibson, Herbert (Box A-108, Folder 11)
    - Scott-Heron, Gil (Box A-108, Folder 12)
    - Scottsboro Boys (Box A-108, Folder 13)
    - Scouting (Box A-108, Folder 14)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Hayes
    - Scranton, William (Box A-108, Folder 15)
    - Screen, Carlton (Box A-108, Folder 16)
    - Screen, Anita (Box A-108, Folder 17)
      Photographer if identified: N.Y. Daily News Photo, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Screen, Mary (Box A-108, Folder 18)
    - Screvane, Paul (Box A-108, Folder 19)
      2 prints have newspaper clipping taped to verso. One print has staple through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Gill Photographers, Bro. David McAdams, Maurey Garber, James Gilbert, Cecil Layne
    - Scribner, Dr. Harvey B. (Box A-108, Folder 20)
      Photographer if identified: NYC Board of Ed., Harris Photo,
    - Scroggins, Joe (Box A-108, Folder 21)
      Photographer if identified: U.S. Merchant Marine Academy
    - Scruggs, Liz (Box A-108, Folder 22)
      Photographer if identified: George M. West
    - Scruggs, Marie (Box A-108, Folder 23)
    - Scruggs, Martin (Box A-108, Folder 24)
    - Scruggs, Ramon (Box A-108, Folder 25)
      Photographer if identified: Leon Perry
    - Scrutchions, Cleophus (Box A-108, Folder 26)
    - Scurlock, Herbert A. (Box A-108, Folder 27)
    - "The Sea Gypsies" (Box A-108, Folder 28)
    - Sea Lion (Box A-108, Folder 29)
    - Seabron, William M. (Box A-108, Folder 30)
    - Seaborne, Reginald (Box A-108, Folder 31)
    - Seaborn, Ernestine (Box A-108, Folder 32)
    - Larry Seabrook (Box A-108, Folder 33)
    - Seabrook, Luther W. (Box A-108, Folder 34)
    - Seaga, Edward (Mrs.) Mitsy (Box A-108, Folder 35)
    - Seaga, Edward (Box A-108, Folder 36)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, A. F. Sabo Assoc., Elizabeth Marshall,
    - Seagrams (Box A-108, Folder 37)
      3 prints are stuck together with paste. 2 prints have newspaper clipping taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Tommy Weber, Morgan,
    - Seale, Archie E. (Box A-108, Folder 38)
      Also flier for relief fund for riot victims.
    - Seale, Bobby (Box A-108, Folder 39)
    - Seale, Bobby Mrs. & Son (Box A-108, Folder 40)
    - Seale, Cecil A. (Box A-108, Folder 41)
      Photographer if identified: Dick De Marsico
    - Seale, Eugene A. (Box A-108, Folder 42)
      Photographer if identified: Robert B. Grubb
    - Seale, Laura (Mrs.) (Box A-108, Folder 43)
    - Seales, Joseph L. III (Box A-108, Folder 44)
    - Seals, Son (Box A-108, Folder 45)
      Photographer if identified: Steve Kagan
    - Sealy, Adrienne (Box A-108, Folder 46)
      Photographer if identified: King Photographers, Dave Greene, Tom McManus,
    - Sealy, Charles (Box A-108, Folder 47)
    - Sealy, Desmond H. (Box A-108, Folder 48)
    - Sealy, Eloise (Box A-108, Folder 49)
    - Sealy, Estelle (Mrs. Lloyd) (see Lucretia Collins) (Box A-108, Folder 50)
    - Sealy, Margaret Lillian (Box A-108, Folder 51)
      Both prints have staples through edge.
    - Sealy, Milt (Box A-108, Folder 52)
    - Sealy, Percival P. (Box A-108, Folder 53)
    - Sealy, Ruby (Box A-108, Folder 54)
      Also one velox print. One print is a Polaroid, with staple through edge.
    - Sealy, Rubert (Box A-108, Folder 55)
    - Sealy, Theodore (Box A-108, Folder 56)
    - Sealy, W. V. (Box A-108, Folder 57)
    - Sealy, Wally (Box A-108, Folder 58)
    - Sealy, Warwick (Box A-108, Folder 59)
      Also one velox print, and one halftone print. 1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Cecil Layne, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Tommy Weber
    - Searles, Joseph (Box A-108, Folder 60)
      Photographer if identified: L. St. Clair Dummett, Blacker-Amster
    - Searles, Pal (Box A-108, Folder 61)
    - Sears, Florence (Box A-108, Folder 62)
    - Sears, Floyd Dr. (Box A-108, Folder 63)
    - Sears, Judy (Box A-108, Folder 64)
    - Sears, India (Box A-108, Folder 65)
    - Sears, Nora (Box A-108, Folder 66)
    - Sease, Marvin (Box A-108, Folder 67)
      Autographed by Sease.
    - Seaver, Tom (Box A-108, Folder 68)
    - Seavers, Cecil A. (Box A-108, Folder 69)
    - Seavs, Floyd Dr. (Box A-108, Folder 70)
    - Sebro, Anthony (Box A-108, Folder 71)
    - Sebron, Carolyn (Box A-108, Folder 72)
    - Secka, Mamadou Johnny (Box A-108, Folder 73)
    - Second Canaan Baptist Church (Box A-108, Folder 74)
      Photographer if identified: Alvin's Photo Service, David McAdams, Blake Photographers
    - "Section" (Box A-108, Folder 75)
    - Sedfire (Box A-108, Folder 76)
      Photographer if identified: John D. Herman,
    - SEEK Program (Box A-108, Folder 77)
      Photographer if identified: Paul Sheridan, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, David McAdams, Harris Photo
    - Seeling, Ellen (Box A-108, Folder 78)
    - Seely, Estelle (Box A-108, Folder 79)
    - Seeman, Aubrey (Box A-108, Folder 80)
    - Segal, George (Box A-108, Folder 81)
      One print has staple through edge. 1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Photography by MUKY
    - Segal, Mort (Box A-108, Folder 82)
    - Segee, Mildred (Box A-108, Folder 83)
      Photographer if identified: Internal Revenue Service
    - Segun, Festus O. (Rev.) (Box A-108, Folder 84)
    - Seivwright, Edna (Box A-108, Folder 85)
    - Seixas, Harry (Box A-108, Folder 86)
      Photographer if identified: Frutchey Associates
    - Sekka, Johnny (Box A-108, Folder 87)
    - Selby, Dayton (Box A-108, Folder 88)
    - Selby, Virginia (Box A-108, Folder 89)
    - Seldin, Abe (Box A-108, Folder 90)
    - Bruce Seldon (Box A-108, Folder 91)
    - Selene, Princess (Box A-108, Folder 92)
    - Self Help Group (Box A-108, Folder 93)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Dave Greene
    - Robert Sell (Box A-108, Folder 94)
    - Sellers, Butler J. (Box A-108, Folder 95)
    - Sellers, Cleveland (Box A-108, Folder 96)
      Photographer if identified: SOBU Staff Photo, Wide World Photos
    - Sellers, John (Brother) (Box A-108, Folder 97)
    - Sellers, Joseph PS 200 Principal (Box A-108, Folder 98)
    - Sellers, Lois B. Dr. (Box A-108, Folder 99)
    - Sellers, Marlon (Box A-108, Folder 100)
    - Sellers, Peter (Box A-108, Folder 101)
    - Sellers, Phil (Box A-108, Folder 102)
    - Sellers, Tommy (Box A-108, Folder 103)
    - Selmone, Beverly (Box A-108, Folder 104)
    - Selsey, Senora (Box A-108, Folder 105)
    - Ousmane Sembue (Box A-108, Folder 106)
    - Semedo, Julio (Box A-108, Folder 107)
      Photographer if identified: M. Tzovaras/United Nations
    - Semple, Ronald Bobb (Box A-108, Folder 108)
      Print has CV stapled to verso.
    - Semple, Shirley N. (Box A-108, Folder 109)
      Photographer if identified: Ulysses Allen Providence
    - Imahoy Kristos Semia (Box A-108, Folder 110)
    - Sena, Wilma (Box A-108, Folder 111)
    - Sendwe, Jason (Box A-108, Folder 112)
    - Seneca, Joe (Box A-108, Folder 113)
    - Senegalese Dancers (Box A-108, Folder 114)
      Photographer if identified: George Kalinsky, Pictorial Enterprise, Associated Press, Harris Photo
    - Sengestacke, John (Box A-108, Folder 115)
    - Senghor, Loepold Sedar (Box A-108, Folder 116)
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos, Friedman-Abeles
    - Senior, Clarence (Box A-108, Folder 117)
    - Senior Citizens (Box A-108, Folder 118)
      Also 5 velox prints. 3 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Standard Studios, Dave Greene, King Photographers, A. Hansen, Bill Mitchell, Camera Arts Studio, Bill Price,
    - Senior Citizens (Box A-108, Folder 119)
      Also 3 velox prints. One print has staple through edge. 3 prints stapled together.
      Photographer if identified: King Photographers, Dave Greene, Wagner International Photos, Emma Rivera, Robert Velez, Alex Summers, Peterkin Photo, Tex Harris
    - Senior Citizens (Box A-108, Folder 120)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, L. St. Clair Dummett, Lensman, Alex Summers, Larry Brown, King Photographers,
    - Senior Citizens (Box A-108, Folder 121)
      Photographer if identified: Marilyn Mitchell, Pictorial Enterprise, Lloyd Yearwood,
    - Senior, Irving Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-108, Folder 122)
    - Seniors, Robert (Box A-108, Folder 123)
    - Sensational Nightingales (Box A-108, Folder 124)
      Photographer if identified: Michael Denning
    - Senstache, John (Box A-108, Folder 125)
    - Sentimental Soul (Box A-108, Folder 126)
    - "Sepia Star" (Box A-108, Folder 127)
      Photographer if identified: Roger Greenawalt
    - Sepyo, Jim (Box A-108, Folder 128)
    - Sergio (Box A-108, Folder 129)
    - Serling, Rod (Box A-108, Folder 130)
    - Serrano, Alfredo (Box A-108, Folder 131)
    - Serrano, Elena (Box A-108, Folder 132)
    - Serrette, Dennis (Box A-108, Folder 133)
    - Sertima, Van (Family) (Box A-108, Folder 134)
    - Service, Russell (Box A-108, Folder 135)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Rufus Merritt, Studio of the New York Times, Phillip Kaye Studio
    - Sesame Street (Box A-108, Folder 136)
    - Sesame Street (Box A-108, Folder 137)
    - Sete, Bola (Box A-108, Folder 138)
    - Settle, Joseph C. Dr. (Box A-108, Folder 139)
    - Seven Investors Club (Box A-108, Folder 140)
    - Seven Souls (Box A-108, Folder 141)
    - Seventh Day Adventist (Box A-108, Folder 142)
    - The Seventh Principle (Box A-108, Folder 143)
    - Sevier, Grace (Mrs.) (Box A-108, Folder 144)
    - Seville, Johnny (Box A-108, Folder 145)
    - Seville, Soul (Box A-108, Folder 146)
      Photographer if identified: Laurie Paladino
    - Sevillian, Mary (Box A-108, Folder 147)
    - Sewall, Clifford (Box A-108, Folder 148)
      Photographer if identified: Fabian Bachrach, Jamaica Tourist Board
    - Seward, Aaron (Box A-108, Folder 149)
    - Seward, Granville Rev. (Box A-108, Folder 150)
    - Seward Park High School Quintet (Box A-108, Folder 151)
    - Sewell, Alfred (Box A-108, Folder 152)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Photography by Leon, James Gilbert,
    - Carl Sewell Dr. (Box A-108, Folder 153)
    - Sewell, Clifford (Box A-108, Folder 154)
    - Sewell, Douglas Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-108, Folder 155)
    - Sewell, Katie (Box A-108, Folder 156)
      3 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Mr. A. Brenners, David McAdams,
    - Sewell, Newton (Box A-108, Folder 157)
    - Sewere, Fuzzy (Box A-108, Folder 158)
    - Sexton, Clarence Rev. (Box A-108, Folder 159)
    - Sexton, Edwin T. (Box A-108, Folder 160)
    - Sexton, Henri (Box A-108, Folder 161)
    - Sexton, James Jr. (Box A-108, Folder 162)
    - Seye, Abdou (Box A-108, Folder 163)
    - Seymour, Cecelia (Box A-108, Folder 164)
      Photographer if identified: Miss Luckett
    - Seymour, Frank (Box A-108, Folder 165)
    - Seymour, Herbert E. (Box A-108, Folder 166)
      Photographer if identified: Rudy Castillo Studio
    - Seymour, Lafayette R. (Box A-108, Folder 167)
    - Seymour, Rosalie A. (Box A-108, Folder 168)
    - Seymour, Whitney North (Jr.) (Box A-108, Folder 169)
    - Seymour Lundy Assoc. (Box A-108, Folder 170)
    - "Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band" (Box A-108, Folder 171)
      Photo is of Earth, Wind, and Fire.
    - Sha Na Na (Box A-108, Folder 172)
    - Sha Na Na (Box A-108, Folder 173)
    - Sha, Sekwy (Box A-108, Folder 174)
    - Shabazz, Abu (Box A-108, Folder 175)
    - Shabazz, Attallah (Box A-108, Folder 176)
    - Shabazz, James (Box A-108, Folder 177)
    - Shabazz, Jeremiah S. (Box A-108, Folder 178)
    - Shabazz, Jeremiah S. M. (Box A-108, Folder 179)
    - Shabazz, John (Box A-108, Folder 180)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Pictorial Enterprise,
    - Shabazz, Lana (Box A-108, Folder 181)
    - Shackleton, Cecil (Box A-108, Folder 182)
      Polaroid print taped to cardboard.
      Photographer if identified: B. Schulman
    - Shackley, Fred (Box A-108, Folder 183)
      Photographer if identified: GM Photographic
    - Shade, William (Box A-108, Folder 184)
    - Shades (Box A-108, Folder 185)
      Photographer if identified: Daniela Federici
    - Shades of Love (Box A-108, Folder 186)
    - Shadlow, Merriel (Box A-108, Folder 187)
    - Shadow & Echoes (Box A-108, Folder 188)
    - Shaffer, John H. (Box A-108, Folder 189)
    - Shagari, Alhaji Shehu (Box A-108, Folder 190)
      1 halftone print, 2 color laser prints, 1 biographical booklet.
    - Shah, Kansin C. (Box A-108, Folder 191)
    - Shakespeare Institute (Box A-108, Folder 192)
      Photographer if identified: Martha Swope, Bert Andrews,
    - Shalamar (Box A-108, Folder 193)
      Photographer if identified: David Zahner
    - Shamberger, James P. Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-108, Folder 194)
    - Shane, Mrs. Glen Howard (Box A-108, Folder 195)
    - Shane, Joanne (Box A-108, Folder 196)
    - Shane, Ronald Mr. (Box A-108, Folder 197)
    - Shangay (Box A-108, Folder 198)
    - Shange, Ntozake (Box A-108, Folder 199)
    - Shange, Sikhulu (Box A-108, Folder 200)
    - Shange, Sikhulu (Box A-108, Folder 201)
    - "Shango" (Box A-108, Folder 202)
    - Shankar, Verinda (Box A-108, Folder 203)
    - Shanker, Albert (Box A-108, Folder 204)
      Photographer if identified: Karsh, Ottawa
    - Shanker, Albert (Box A-108, Folder 205)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Whitestone Photo, Dan Miller, Karsh, Ottawa
    - Shanklin, Harry (Box A-108, Folder 206)
    - Shann, Lamarr (Box A-108, Folder 207)
    - Shannon (Box A-108, Folder 208)
    - Shannon, David T. Rev. (Box A-108, Folder 209)
    - Shannon, Edward J. Sr. (Box A-108, Folder 210)
    - Shannon, Foster (Box A-108, Folder 211)
    - Shannon, Gloria (Box A-108, Folder 212)
    - Shannon, Jacqui (Box A-108, Folder 213)
    - Shannon, John (Box A-108, Folder 214)
      Photographer if identified: Ron Ebson/US Army
    - Shannon, Ruth (Box A-108, Folder 215)
    - Shapiro, Elliott (Dr.) (Box A-108, Folder 216)
    - Shapp, Charles (Dr.) (Box A-108, Folder 217)
    - Sharp Electronics (Box A-108, Folder 218)
    - Sharp, Charlie M. Mrs. (Box A-108, Folder 219)
    - Sharp, Dee Dee (Box A-108, Folder 220)
      Photographer if identified: Michael Denning, Pan American World Airways
    - Sharp, Saundra (Box A-108, Folder 221)
      Also one halftone print. One print has staple through edge. 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
      Photographer if identified: Martin,
    - Sharp, William (Box A-108, Folder 222)
    - Sharpe, Altonese (Box A-108, Folder 223)
    - Sharpe, Baldwin (Box A-108, Folder 224)
    - Sharpe, Charles W. (Box A-108, Folder 225)
    - Sharpe, Elza R. (Box A-108, Folder 226)
    - Sharpe, Helen (Box A-108, Folder 227)
      Photographer if identified: Bro. David McAdams, Tommy Comer
    - Sharpe, Jaqueline (Box A-108, Folder 228)
    - Sharpe, Linda (Box A-108, Folder 229)
    - Sharpe, Lynn (Box A-108, Folder 230)
    - Sharpe, Marva (Box A-108, Folder 231)
    - Sharpe, Romolia (Box A-108, Folder 232)
      Photographer if identified: Michael Feinstein
    - Sharpe, Rudolph (Box A-108, Folder 233)
    - Sharper, Hazel (Box A-108, Folder 234)
      Photographer if identified: Burley, James Gilbert, M Associates
    - Sharpless, Mattie (Box A-108, Folder 235)
    - Al Sharpton (Box A-108, Folder 236)
      Also 1 photocopy. 4 prints have staple. 1 print has typescript caption stapled to recto. 3 prints stapled together.
      Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Bob George, Curt Clemons, Pictorial Enterprise, Errol Sawyer, Dan Kaplan, Kathy Beckam, Peterkin Photo, Michael Klein, James Larkins,
    - Al Sharpton (Box A-108, Folder 237)
      Also 3 photocopies. 2 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has typescript caption stapled to recto.
      Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Michael Clopton, Anthony Charles, Chi Modu, Michael Klein, Bob George, Bill Moore, Yvonne Holmes, James Larkin, United African Movement Photo Department, Christopher Griffith,
    - Sharpton Photo (Box A-108, Folder 238)
      Also 1 facsimile newspaper clipping. 2 prints stapled together. 3 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Peterkin Photo, Bill Moore, Curt Clemons,
    - Sharrin! (Box A-108, Folder 239)
      7 prints of Al Sharpton.
      Photographer if identified: Norm Harris, Lichtman
    - Sharrock, Kimberly (Box A-108, Folder 240)
    - Shavers, Blanche (Box A-108, Folder 241)
      Photographer if identified: Beuford Smith/Burley Photo Service
    - Shavers, Charlie (Box A-108, Folder 242)
    - Shavers, Darrell (Box A-108, Folder 243)
      Photographer if identified: Bunny Photo Studio, Ernest Agnew
    - Shavers, Earnie (Box A-108, Folder 244)
    - Shavers, Yvonne (Box A-108, Folder 245)
    - Shaw, Arvel (Box A-108, Folder 246)
      Photographer if identified: Nancy Kaye
    - Barrington D. Shaw (Box A-108, Folder 247)
    - Shaw, Bernard (Box A-108, Folder 248)
    - Shaw, Geraldine (Box A-108, Folder 249)
    - Shaw, Geoge Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-108, Folder 250)
    - Bishop Herbert Bell Shaw (Box A-108, Folder 251)
    - Shaw, James H. (Box A-108, Folder 252)
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene, Monclova Photographers
    - Shaw, James (Johnnie) (Box A-108, Folder 253)
    - Shaw, Joan (Box A-108, Folder 254)
    - Shaw, Judy (Box A-108, Folder 255)
    - Shaw, Kenneth E. Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-108, Folder 265)
    - Shaw, Larry (Box A-109, Folder 1)
    - Shaw, Lee (Box A-109, Folder 2)
      Photographer if identified: Sam Siegel
    - Shaw, Leslie N. (Box A-109, Folder 3)
    - Shaw, Margie (Box A-109, Folder 4)
    - Shaw, Mariena (Box A-109, Folder 5)
    - Shaw, N. (Box A-109, Folder 6)
      Photographer if identified: James Pozarik
    - Shaw, Nan (Box A-109, Folder 7)
    - Shaw, Noel (Box A-109, Folder 8)
    - Shaw, Patricia (Box A-109, Folder 9)
    - Shaw, Robert (Box A-109, Folder 10)
      Photographer if identified: Daniel Edelman
    - Shaw, Robert R. (Box A-109, Folder 11)
    - Shaw, Sam (Box A-109, Folder 12)
      Also 2 velox prints
      Photographer if identified: Columbia Pictures
    - Shaw, Stan (Box A-109, Folder 13)
    - Shaw, Thomas H. (Dr.) (Box A-109, Folder 14)
    - Shaw University (Box A-109, Folder 15)
      Approximately four prints have single-leaf carbon typescript releases stapled or attached to prints with paperclips.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, J.D. Hinton Photo, Rufus Merritt, The News Bureau/Shaw University
    - Shaw, Vanessa (Box A-109, Folder 16)
    - Shaw, Woody (Box A-109, Folder 17)
    - Shaw, William (Dr.) (Box A-109, Folder 18)
    - Shawarbi (Dr.) (Box A-109, Folder 19)
      Also one four-leaf typescript release attached with paperclip.
    - Shay, Michele (Box A-109, Folder 20)
    - Shea Stadium (Box A-109, Folder 21)
    - Shea, Thomas (Box A-109, Folder 22)
    - Shea, Wm. F. (Box A-109, Folder 23)
      Photographer if identified: King Photographers, YMCA of Greater New York
    - Shearer, Hugh (Box A-109, Folder 24)
      One print housed in folded board frame with design on front.
      Photographer if identified: Maurey Garber, Jamaica Tourist Board/Anthony Russell, James Gilbert, Ventura Photo Service
    - Shearer, John (Box A-109, Folder 25)
    - Shearer, Kathleen (Box A-109, Folder 26)
    - Shearer, Phyllis (Box A-109, Folder 27)
      Photographer if identified: George Tiplady
    - Shearer, Ted (Box A-109, Folder 28)
      Photographer if identified: John Shearer
    - Shearer, Reuben A. (Rev.) (Box A-109, Folder 29)
    - Shearn, Placida (Box A-109, Folder 30)
    - "Sheba, Baby" (Box A-109, Folder 31)
    - Sheeler, J. Reuben (Dr.) (Box A-109, Folder 32)
      Photographer if identified: Mae Kyles
    - Sheen, Fulton J. (Bishop) (Box A-109, Folder 33)
      Photographer if identified: Shields, The Salvation Army
    - Sheer Movement (Box A-109, Folder 34)
    - Sheer Silk Stocking Club (Box A-109, Folder 35)
    - Sheffey, Howard L. (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-109, Folder 36)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Police Department
    - Sheffield, Jennifer (Box A-109, Folder 37)
    - Sheffer, Haley (Box A-109, Folder 38)
    - Shell, Joseph (Box A-109, Folder 39)
    - Shell, Theresa (Box A-109, Folder 40)
    - Shellman, Eugene (Box A-109, Folder 41)
    - Shelman, Herbert (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-109, Folder 42)
    - Shelter, McMahon (Box A-109, Folder 43)
      Photographer if identified: Ivan Photo
    - Shelton, Alvin (Box A-109, Folder 44)
    - Shelton, Betty J. (Box A-109, Folder 45)
    - Shelton, Bill (Karen) (Box A-109, Folder 46)
    - Shelton, Carole P. (Box A-109, Folder 47)
      Photographer if identified: Jan W. Faul
    - Shelton, Edith (Box A-109, Folder 48)
    - Shelton, Howard (Box A-109, Folder 49)
    - Shelton, Johnny and Gloria Shelton (Box A-109, Folder 50)
    - Shelton, Lonnie (Box A-109, Folder 51)
    - Shelton, Patricia (Box A-109, Folder 52)
    - Shelton, S. McDowell (Bishop) (Box A-109, Folder 53)
      Also three releases, each on two leaves, stapled to borders of prints.
      Photographer if identified: Punjab Photo Service, Dufor Photographers, Studio One, Fabian Bachrach
    - Shelton, S. McDowell (Bishop) (Box A-109, Folder 54)
    - Shelton, Samuel B., Jr. (Box A-109, Folder 55)
      Photographer if identified: U.S. Army Photograph/Central Photo Facility/Fort Jay NY
    - Shelton, Robert E. (Box A-109, Folder 56)
    - Shelton, Walter (Box A-109, Folder 57)
    - Shemah, Star (Box A-109, Folder 58)
    - Shep and The Limelites (Box A-109, Folder 59)